A Guide to the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission Yucca Mountain Research Collection TD898.12.N3 U85
University of Nevada, Reno. DeLaMare Science & Engineering Library
- U.S. Supreme Court. "Whitman v. American Trucking Associations." (Box 133, Folder 9)
- Weart, S.R. "Nuclear fear, a history of images." (Box 133, Folder 10)
- Williams, R. "[Nye County population estimates through the fourth quarter. Memorandum]." (Box 133, Folder 11)
- Williams, N.H. "[Contract no. DE-AC08-01RW12101 - total system performance assessment sensitivity analyses for final nuclear regulatory commission regulations. Letter to S.J. Brocoum, DOE]." Bechtel Saic Company LLC. (Box 133, Folder 12)
- Williams, N.H. "[Contract no. DE-AC-08-01NV12101 - submittal of deliverable repository surface design. Letter to S.J. Brocoum, DOE]." Bechtel Saic Company LLC. (Box 133, Folder 13)
- Williams, N.H. "[Contract no. DE-AC-08-01NV12101 - submittal of letter update to 'engineering files - subsurface repository.' Letter to S.J. Brocoum, DOE]." Bechtel Saic Company LLC. (Box 133, Folder 14)
- Williams, N.H. "[Contract no. DE-AC-08-01RW12101 - corrections to final letter report describing the performance of proposed Yucca Mountain repository. Letter to J.R. Summerson, DOE]." Bechtel Saic Company LLC. (Box 133, Folder 15)
- Williams, N.H. and Levy, L.E. "The desert space station science museum, contributions to the Nye County and Nevada economies." Nye County economic-demographic reports #7." Nye County Department of Natural Resources and history. (Box 133, Folder 16)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Milestone SP32IM3. Vol. 1 ch. 1-5. (Box 134, Folder 1)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Milestone SP32IM3. Vol. 1 ch. 6-9 (Box 134, Folder 2)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Milestone SP32IM3. Vol. 2 appendices A-D. (Box 134, Folder 3)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Milestone SP32IM3. Vol. 2 appendix E. (Box 134, Folder 4)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Milestone SP32IM3. Vol. 3 appendices F-J. (Box 134, Folder 5)
- Wu, Y.S., Chen, G., and Bodvarsson, G. "Preliminary analysis of effects of thermal loading on gas and heat flow within the framework of the LBNL/USGS site-scale model." Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory. LBL-37729. (Box 135, Folder 1)
- West Valley Nuclear Services Co. "West Valley demonstration project, site environmental report, calendar year 1999." (Box 135, Folder 2)
- Yang, I.C., Rattray, G.W. and Yu, P. "Interpretation of chemical and isotopic data from boreholes in the unsaturated zone at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Water-resources investigations report 96-4058. (Box 135, Folder 3)
- Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project. "Evaluation of the potentially adverse condition 'evidence of extreme erosion during the quaternary period' at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." (Box 135, Folder 4)
- Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project. "Technical basis report for surface characteristics, preclosure hydrology, and erosion." YMP.TBR-0001, Rev 0. (Box 135, Folder 5)
- Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project. "Land cover types in the proposed land withdrawal area." YMP-98-094.2. (Box 135, Folder 6)
- Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project. "Proposed land withdrawal area." YMP-98-200.0 (Box 135, Folder 7)
- Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project. "Reclamation implementation plan." YMP/91-14, Rev. 2. (Box 135, Folder 8)
- Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project. "[PETT and tax numbers Email communication to P. Baxter, DOE]." (Box 135, Folder 9)
- Yoshimura, H.R. and Huerta, M. "Full-scale tests of spent nuclear-fuel shipping systems [document removed]." (Box 135, Folder 10)
- Yoshimura, H.R. "Full scale simulations of accidents on spent-nuclear fuel shipping systems [document removed]." (Box 135, Folder 11)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Indices to NRC microfiche collections.", undated (Box 135, Folder 12)
- "Microfiche documentation.", undated (Box 136, Folder 1)
- "Nuclear Regulatory Commission microfiche documentation.", undated (Box 136, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Document room directory revision paperwork." (Box 136, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Filing instructions for high-level waste documents.", undated (Box 136, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Citizen's guide to U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission information." (Box 136, Folder 5)
- "Nuclear Regulatory Commission microfiche documentation.", undated (Box 137, Folder 1)
- "Nuclear Regulatory Commission microfiche statistics.", undated (Box 137, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Weekly announcement of NRC staff meetings open to the public." 30 June 1997-29 September 1997. (Box 138, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Weekly announcement of NRC staff meetings open to the public." 6 October 1997-29 December 1997. (Box 138, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Weekly announcement of NRC staff meetings open to the public." 5 January 1998-30 March 1998. (Box 138, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Weekly announcement of NRC staff meetings open to the public." 6 April 1998-22 June 1998. (Box 138, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Weekly announcement of NRC staff meetings open to the public." 6 July 1998-28 September 1998. (Box 138, Folder 5)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Weekly announcement of NRC staff meetings open to the public." 5 October 1998-28 December 1998. (Box 138, Folder 6)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Weekly announcement of NRC staff meetings open to the public." 4 January 1999-22 February 1999. (Box 138, Folder 7)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Weekly announcement of NRC staff meetings open to the public." 1 March 1999-26 April 1999. (Box 138, Folder 8)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Weekly announcement of NRC staff meetings open to the public." 3 May 1999-26 July 1999. (Box 138, Folder 9)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Weekly announcement of NRC staff meetings open to the public." 2 August 1999-18 October 1999. (Box 138, Folder 10)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "LPDR weekly accession list." (Box 139, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "LPDR weekly accession list." (Box 139, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "LPDR weekly accession list." (Box 139, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1978-1983, undated (Box 140, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1984., undated (Box 140, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." January 1985-June 1985., undated (Box 140, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." July 1985-December 1985., undated (Box 140, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." January 1986-June 1986., undated (Box 141, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." July 1986-December 1986., undated (Box 141, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." January 1987-June 1987., undated (Box 141, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." July 1987-December 1987., undated (Box 141, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." January 1988-June 1988., undated (Box 142, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." July 1988-December 1988., undated (Box 142, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." December 1988-December 1989., undated (Box 142, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list contract files related to project WM-11." A-0294 to A-1757., undated (Box 143, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list contract files related to project WM-11." A-3163 to A-3168., undated (Box 143, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list contract files related to project WM-11." A-4165 to A-7150., undated (Box 143, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list contract files related to project WM-11." B-02887 to B-0290., undated (Box 143, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list contract files related to project WM-11." B-6934 to B-6986., undated (Box 144, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list contract files related to project WM-11." B-7327 to B-7390., undated (Box 144, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list contract files related to project WM-11." D-1003 to D-1662., undated (Box 144, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1978-1987., undated (Box 145, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1988., undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1989., undated (Box 145, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1990., undated (Box 145, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1990-1991., undated (Box 146, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1992., undated (Box 146, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1993., undated (Box 146, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1994., undated (Box 147, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1995., undated (Box 147, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Cumulative accession list project WM-11." 1996., undated (Box 147, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 148, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 148, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 148, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 149, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 149, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 149, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 150, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 150, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 150, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 151, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 151, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 151, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 151, Folder 4)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 152, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 152, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 152, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 152, Folder 4)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 153, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 153, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 153, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 154, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 154, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 154, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 154, Folder 4)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 155, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 155, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 155, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 156, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 156, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 156, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 156, Folder 4)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 157, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 157, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 157, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 157, Folder 4)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 158, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 158, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 158, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 159, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 159, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 159, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 160, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 160, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 160, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 160, Folder 4)
- Battelle Project Management Division. "Performance assessment plans and methods for the Salt Repository project." (Box 161, Folder 1)
- Waste Management Project Office, U.S. Department of Energy. "Working draft of NNWSI project environmental assessment." (Box 161, Folder 2)
- "NNWSI/NRC geochemistry workshop July 10-12, 1984 Los Alamos National Laboratory." (Box 161, Folder 3)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 161, Folder 4)
- Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Materials requested by NRC." Part 1 of 2. (Box 162, Folder 1)
- Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Materials requested by NRC." Part 2 of 2. (Box 162, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI weekly highlights for week ending September 13, 1984." (Box 162, Folder 3)
- Coplan, S. "[Request for site-specific samples for contractor Oak Ridge National Laboratories to be used in experiments studying radionuclide solubilities and selected retardation parameters. Letter to Blanchard, M.B., DOE, with attachments]." Division of Waste Management, Office of Nuclear Material Safety and Safeguards. (Box 163, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NRC-DOE geochemistry meeting summary July 10-12, 1984." (Box 163, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 163, Folder 3)
- Lee, R.R. "[EA scoping review in geology-geophysics. Memorandum to Justus, P.S. (Waste Management) with attachments]." (Box 163, Folder 4)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI DOE-NRC meeting December 13-14, 1984." (Box 164, Folder 1)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 164, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report weeks of Nov 19 and 26, 1984." (Box 164, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report weeks of Dec 3, 10 and 17, 1984." (Box 164, Folder 4)
- Office of Nuclear Reactor Regulation. "NRR comments on draft environmental assessments for DOE high level waste geologic repository sites." (Box 164, Folder 5)
- Geographic Data Systems. "[Nuclear waste route and reactor maps].", undated (Box 164, Folder 6)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI DOE/NRC summary meeting notes." (Box 165, Folder 1)
- Geographic Data Systems. "[Nuclear waste rail and truck route maps].", undated (Box 165, Folder 2)
- "EA review in geology/geophysics meeting notes." (Box 165, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report weeks of Jan 28 and Feb 4, 1985." (Box 166, Folder 1)
- Bettelle Project Management Division. "References used in environmental assessment reports." (Box 166, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NNWSI project geochemistry presentation to January TPO meeting." (Box 166, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC review of DOE environmental assessment." Vol. 1 of 2. (Box 166, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC review of DOE environmental assessment." Vol. 2 of 2. (Box 166, Folder 5)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "SCP management plan." (Box 167, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report weeks of May 20, 27 and June 3, 1985." (Box 167, Folder 2)
- "Project WM-11: Potential high-level radioactive waste geologic repository site Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 167, Folder 3)
- "NRC/SRP management meeting record." (Box 168, Folder 1)
- Waste Management Project Office, U.S. Department of Energy. "WBS dictionary and NNWSI project milestone listing." (Box 168, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report for weeks of June 10, 17 and 24, 1985." (Box 168, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report for weeks of July 1,8, 15 and 22, 1985." (Box 168, Folder 4)
- "NRC-NNWSI project waste package meeting summary July 23-24, 1985." (Box 169, Folder 1)
- "NRC-NNWSI project exploratory shaft design/construction meeting summary Aug 27-28, 1985." (Box 169, Folder 2)
- Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory. "LLNL monthly reports." (Box 169, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report Oct 1-Oct 18, 1985." (Box 169, Folder 4)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report period 10/19-11/22/85." (Box 169, Folder 5)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report 5/10/1986-6/17/86." (Box 170, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report 2/15/86-3/21/86." (Box 170, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NTS standard construction specifications." (Box 170, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report Dec 16, 1985-Feb 14, 1986." (Box 171, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Draft chapters of NNWSI project site characterization plan." (Box 171, Folder 2)
- Muth, T.R. "The effects of welding and casting process variables on the microstructure and properties of high level nuclear waste overpack containers." Department of Metallurgical Engineering, Colorado School of Mines. (Box 171, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report 8/20-10/10/86." Vol. 1 of 2. (Box 172, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "NNWSI site report 8/20-10/10/86." Vol. 2 of 2. (Box 172, Folder 2)
- "Preliminary results of staff investigation into DOE selection of 3 sites." (Box 172, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 173, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 173, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 173, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 173, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 173, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 174, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 173, Folder 7)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 173, Folder 8)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 174, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 174, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 174, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 174, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 174, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 174, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-0294." (Box 174, Folder 7)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 175, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 175, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 175, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 175, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 175, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 175, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 176, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 176, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 176, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 176, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 176, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1158." (Box 176, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 177, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 177, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 177, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 177, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 177, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 177, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 178, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 178, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 178, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 178, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 178, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1165." (Box 178, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1166." (Box 179, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1166." (Box 179, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1166." (Box 179, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1166." (Box 179, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1168." (Box 179, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1755." (Box 180, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1755." (Box 180, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1755." (Box 180, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1755." (Box 180, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1755." (Box 180, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1755." (Box 180, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1755." (Box 180, Folder 7)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1755." (Box 180, Folder 8)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 181, Folder 1)